campus
entrance
courtyard
schedule
notice board
uniform
enter
classroom
desk
whiteboard
notebook
lesson
question
answer
library
bookshelf
dictionary
page
title
library card
borrow
cafeteria
tray
menu
lunch
soup
seat
order
playground
basketball court
soccer field
whistle
teamwork
scoreboard
practice
hallway
locker
backpack
assignment
dismissal
review
auditorium
gymnasium
laboratory
art room
music room
nurse's office
principal's office
dormitory
computer lab
assembly hall
staircase
parking lot
pencil
eraser
ruler
marker
textbook
workbook
folder
calculator
glue
scissors
compass
stapler
attendance
homework
project
presentation
experiment
exam
grade
recess
club
semester
timetable
graduation